visareservation.com 2018-12-30

# Privacy Policy - Visa Reservation

_**Revised: May 23, 2018**_

When you purchase something from our website, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal data you give us such as your name, Phone number, address, email address, passport number(optional), Age, Gender, Date of Birth, Citizenship, Beneficiary name and relationship.

 **EU PERSONAL DATA**

If you are located in the EU, United Kingdom, Lichtenstein, Norway, or Iceland, you may have additional rights under the EU General Data Protection Regulation (the “GDPR”) related to your Personal Data described above. Visa Reservation will be the controller of your Personal Data processed in connection with the Service. The essential personal data described above is collected online through the website only.

### GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation) – Additional Rights for EEA users or similar international areas

If You live in the European Economic Area, or a similar international area, You may have additional privacy rights available to You under applicable laws. We will process Your requests in accordance with applicable data protection laws. If You would like to exercise any of the below rights, please contact service@visareservation.com so that We may consider Your request in accordance with applicable law:

  *  **Right not to provide or withdraw consent:**  You have the right not to provide or withdraw Your consent at any time.
  *  **Right of access:**  You may have the right to access the Personal Data that You provided Us.
  *  **Right of erasure:**  You may have the right to the erasure of Personal Data that We hold about You.
  *  **Right to object to processing:**  You may have the right to request that Visa Reservation stop processing Your Personal Data and/or to stop sending You marketing communications.
  *  **Right to rectification:**  You may have the right to require Us to correct any of Your Personal Data.

### Examples of how We use Your Personal Data.

  * To provide You with Site and Service
  * To enhance the Site and Service
  * To respond to Your requests or to manage user accounts
  * To provide feedback and understand Our users
  * To monitor the security of the Site or Service
  * To provide You with promotional communications and materials

When you browse our website, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser, location and operating system.

Email marketing (if applicable): With your permission, we may send you emails about our services, new products and other updates.

How do you get my consent?  
When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or request a refund, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.

If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.

How do I withdraw my consent?  
If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at service@visareservation.com.

We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.

All the payments made on the website follow the guidelines set by [PayPal](http://www.paypal.com/) and [Authorize.Net](http://www.authorize.net/)

For more insight, you may also want to read PayPal’s Terms of Service or Privacy Statement by visiting www.paypal.com

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.

However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.

For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.

In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.

As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.

Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.

Links  
When you click on links on our website, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.

We take measures designed to keep your PII (or Personally Identifiable Information) completely secure. The only time it gets shared out is when you consent it to a third party provider to serve your needs.. At all other times, data is stored within our private cloud (we use Google Cloud Platform). We do not allow any other parties to collect this data unless the law dictates we do so.

COOKIES  
Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.

If our website is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products/services to you.

We also collect a lot of user usage data on our website. This will help us to analyze the user traffic to our website. This includes the pages you checked on our website and the country from which you accessed our website, the time spent on our website etc. We may use tools like google analytics to understand our customer segmentation better so that we can serve them better.

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at service@visareservation.com.
